(Sheldon:)Everything is quantifiable.
(Sheldon:)That French fry? A seven.
(Sheldon:)Spider-Man? A nine.
(Sheldon:)The number nine--
oddly, only a four.
(Leonard:)How ridiculous is he?
(Penny:)A hundred.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you're just
assigning random numbers
(Leonard:)to things based on your opinion.
(Sheldon:)No, I'm not.
(Sheldon:)French fries have
three variables--
(Sheldon:)crispiness, saltiness
and shape.
(Sheldon:)Which is why a curly fry
(Sheldon:)only gets a two.
(Sheldon:)If I wanted curls for dinner,
I'd order a clown wig.
(Penny:)Well, a relationship is more
complicated than a French fry.
(Sheldon:)Not according to the work
of Berscheid, Snyder and Omoto.
(Penny:)Oh, what did those
rascals do now?
(Amy:)They developed the Relationship
Closeness Inventory,
(Amy:)which predicts the stability
of a couple based on behavior.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, not to be confused
(Sheldon:)with the French Fry
Goodness Inventory.
(Sheldon:)That's pure Cooper.
(Leonard:)So, this is accurate?
(Sheldon:)It's been around for 25 years,